sogood.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy

 § I. Logging IP Addresses

    *   
1) 

Our different processes do not require to know your ip so we do not know and do not collect any IP address.

§ II. How we use cookies?

  *   
Cookies and web beacons

i) What are cookies and web beacons  

The Website makes use of "cookies" which are installed on the user's computer when he rates a game on the Website. In addition, the advertisers on the Website such as Google Adsense, Google DoubleClick,and Specific Media (the "Advertisers"), might use "cookies" and/or "web beacons". Cookies are small electronic files that are placed on the harddisk of the user's computer whereas web beacons are mostly clear picture files which are used to keep track of a user's navigation through a single website or a series of websites.

(ii) For what purposes will these cookies and web beacons be used

The Website Owner might use the information stored in a "cookie" in order prevent a user from rating the same game for several times. Such cookies will only be valid for a period of two weeks.

The Advertisers might use information gathered by the cookies and/or the web beacons for the purpose of online behavioral advertising and/or multisite advertising. The types of information that is gathered by the cookies and/or web beacons as well as the purpose(s) for which this information is used, are provided in the privacy policy of the Advertiser concerned. The user can consult the privacy policy of the Advertisers by clicking on the name of the Advertiser (as indicated above).

(iii) Refuse cookies, web-beacons and online behavioral advertising

To the extent that the user's browser settings allow for the installation of cookies and web beacons on his computer, he consents with the installation of such cookies on his computer and he accepts that information relating to him may be used for behavioral advertising. The user of the website has the right to object ("opt-out") against online behavioral advertising and the use of cookies or web beacons. Users can opt-out of cookies by visiting the website of the Advertiser concerned or by visiting the website of the Network Advertisers Initiative at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.  

In addition, the user can refuse the installation of cookies and/or web beacons or delete them by adjusting the browser settings on his computer. To learn more on how to adjust the settings of your internet browser, we recommend the user to visit the website of the browser's vendor.

(iv) Liability for cookies and web beacons

The Website Owner can not be held liable for the Advertisers' cookies or web beacons for whatever purposes pursued.

§ III. Security

    *   
1) 

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

§ IV. Controlling your personal information

    *   
1) 

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

§ V. Advertising

    *   
1) 

[Sogood.com](http://www.sogood.com/) uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

§ VI. Links to other websites

    *   
1) 

[Sogood.com](http://www.sogood.com/) may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

§ VII. Collected Information

  *   
1) 

[Sogood.com](http://www.sogood.com/) receives and stores information that you enter on the website. This includes requested resources, games data etc. This information is stored to improve our processes and track and analyze user activity. All information you enter is voluntary. None of this information is shared with third parties

or if it is grounded on reasons for convenience.

  *   
2) 

The present General terms have been executed on First June 2013.
